BRADLEY LUND

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

◆ SOUTH AFRICA

+27767899191

• DETAILS •

South Africa +27767899191 bradjlund@gmail.com

• LINKS •

LinkedIn

Github

Portfolio Website

SKILLS

JavaScript

Express.js

Node.js

Git

CSS

HTML

SQL

JavaScript

MongoDB

SQL Server Management Studio

SQL Server Reporting Service

React (Basic understanding currently learning)

LANGUAGES

English

Spanish

HOBBIES

Multiple South African champion in Orienteering

Competed for South Africa at the World Orienteering Championships in 2019 in Norway

Ultra-Marathon runner

Ukulele

PROFILE

Hard-working, quick learning Individual with a strong drive to constantly develop myself and enhance my abilities.

An individual with strong interpersonal and communication skills who enjoys working on teams

Gaining a degree in Actuarial Science has given me a firm base and understanding of risk, mathematics, statistics, and probability and taught me how these complex subjects interlink. This background has allowed me to merge these concepts with my development and coding experience, and enhance my problem-solving ability using both of these skill sets.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Business Analyst at Signature Business Solutions - Discovery Invest, Johannesburg September 2020 — Present

Worked in a team, liaising daily with the Accounting team of VatGlobal to build and provide the necessary bank reconciliation requirements.

Provided theses solutions using iCompare, SQL Server Management Studio and SQL Server Reporting Services. This was accomplished by writing efficient stored procedures where complex logic was required.

After automating the processes at VatGlobal sufficiently I am now working on the processes as a consultant at Discovery Invest.

English Teaching Assistant at IES Margarita Salas, Madrid

September 2018 — July 2020

Mathematics and Sciences Tutor at Master Maths, Johannesburg

March 2018 — July 2018

★ OTHER EXPERIENCE

Design and Development of a website for an Independent Musician, Madrid March 2020 — June 2020

Passport Pals, Johannesburg

July 2020 — August 2020

Built a web scraper that scraped Wikipedia data on visa requirements for all countries. Used MongoDB as the database, Express, and Node.js for the back-end. Any two people from two different countries can use the website to see where they can travel to together visa-free.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Actuarial and Financial Mathematics, University of Pretoria, Pretoria

November 2017

COURSES

Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp (Currently Completing), HyperionDev March 2021 — September 2021

Javascript Algorithms and Data Structures, freeCodeCamp

APIs and Microservices, freeCodeCamp

July 2020 — July 2020

MTA: Database Fundamentals (100%), Microsoft

Completed all SQL problems, HackerRank